#### Contact

cristal.williams@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cristal-williams-b49b2314b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
Critical Care
Basic Life Support (BLS)

Certifications
CCRN

# **Cristal Williams**

MSN, RN, CCRN

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

#### Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Burns, Nursing, Critical Care, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Nursing Administration from The University of Texas at Arlington.

### Experience

UT Southwestern Medical Center
Critical Care Registered Nurse, Surgical Intensive Care
September 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Texas Health Resources
Critical Care Registered Nurse
March 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 6 months)
Denton, Texas

Medical City Healthcare (Formerly HCA North Texas) Critical Care RN January 2016 - March 2017 (1 year 3 months) Plano, Texas

TICU, BICU, CCU

Texas Health Resources Critical Care RN August 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 6 months) Dallas, Texas

Trauma intensive care, charge nurse

University medical center Critical Care RN January 2007 - April 2014 (7 years 4 months) TSICU, BICU, RRT, charge nurse

## Education

The University of Texas at Arlington
Master's degree, Nursing Administration · (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Arlington
BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2015 - 2016)

Amarillo College
ADN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2007)